[
  {
    "front": "go",
    "back": "iku",
    "createdAt": 1740158583822
  },
  {
    "front": "to see",
    "back": "miru",
    "createdAt": 1740158594362
  },
  {
    "front": "a lot of",
    "back": "ooi",
    "createdAt": 1740158604299
  },
  {
    "front": "home",
    "back": "ie",
    "createdAt": 1740158613903
  },
  {
    "front": "this",
    "back": "kore",
    "createdAt": 1740158635322
  },
  {
    "front": "that",
    "back": "sore",
    "createdAt": 1740158648141
  },
  {
    "front": "I",
    "back": "watashi",
    "createdAt": 1740158657938
  },
  {
    "front": "work",
    "back": "shigoto",
    "createdAt": 1740158665306
  },
  {
    "front": "when",
    "back": "itsu",
    "createdAt": 1740158673904
  },
  {
    "front": "make",
    "back": "suru",
    "createdAt": 1740158693915
  },
  {
    "front": "leave",
    "back": "deru",
    "createdAt": 1740158701671
  },
  {
    "front": "use",
    "back": "tsukau",
    "createdAt": 1740158721009
  },
  {
    "front": "place",
    "back": "tokoro",
    "createdAt": 1740158729982
  },
  {
    "front": "create",
    "back": "tsukuru",
    "createdAt": 1740158747989
  },
  {
    "front": "think",
    "back": "omou",
    "createdAt": 1740158759815
  },
  {
    "front": "have",
    "back": "motsu",
    "createdAt": 1740158767709
  },
  {
    "front": "buy",
    "back": "kau",
    "createdAt": 1740158776257
  },
  {
    "front": "time",
    "back": "jikan",
    "createdAt": 1740158782451
  },
  {
    "front": "know",
    "back": "shiru",
    "createdAt": 1740158792720
  },
  {
    "front": "same",
    "back": "onaji",
    "createdAt": 1740158799726
  },
  {
    "front": "now",
    "back": "ima",
    "createdAt": 1740158813225
  },
  {
    "front": "new",
    "back": "atarashii",
    "createdAt": 1740158819450
  },
  {
    "front": "become",
    "back": "naru",
    "createdAt": 1740158827047
  },
  {
    "front": "still",
    "back": "mada",
    "createdAt": 1740158853550
  },
  {
    "front": "after",
    "back": "ato",
    "createdAt": 1740158861326
  },
  {
    "front": "hear",
    "back": "kiku",
    "createdAt": 1740158871843
  },
  {
    "front": "tell",
    "back": "iu",
    "createdAt": 1740158886353
  },
  {
    "front": "few",
    "back": "sukunai",
    "createdAt": 1740158900989
  },
  {
    "front": "tall",
    "back": "takai",
    "createdAt": 1740158929995
  },
  {
    "front": "child",
    "back": "kodomo",
    "createdAt": 1740158939850
  },
  {
    "front": "so",
    "back": "sou",
    "createdAt": 1740158948730
  },
  {
    "front": "already",
    "back": "mou",
    "createdAt": 1740158961186
  },
  {
    "front": "student",
    "back": "gakusei",
    "createdAt": 1740158975681
  },
  {
    "front": "hot",
    "back": "atsui",
    "createdAt": 1740158984386
  },
  {
    "front": "please",
    "back": "douzo",
    "createdAt": 1740158990535
  },
  {
    "front": "afternoon",
    "back": "gogo",
    "createdAt": 1740158998951
  },
  {
    "front": "long",
    "back": "nagai",
    "createdAt": 1740159005835
  },
  {
    "front": "book",
    "back": "hon",
    "createdAt": 1740159012315
  },
  {
    "front": "this year",
    "back": "kotoshi",
    "createdAt": 1740159021128
  },
  {
    "front": "often",
    "back": "yoku",
    "createdAt": 1740159031662
  },
  {
    "front": "she",
    "back": "kanojo",
    "createdAt": 1740159055018
  },
  {
    "front": "what",
    "back": "dou",
    "createdAt": 1740159060670
  },
  {
    "front": "word",
    "back": "kotaba",
    "createdAt": 1740159083146
  },
  {
    "front": "face",
    "back": "kao",
    "createdAt": 1740159090136
  },
  {
    "front": "finish",
    "back": "owaru",
    "createdAt": 1740159100278
  },
  {
    "front": "give",
    "back": "ageru",
    "createdAt": 1740159114042
  },
  {
    "front": "like this",
    "back": "kou",
    "createdAt": 1740159131156
  },
  {
    "front": "school",
    "back": "gakkou",
    "createdAt": 1740159140989
  },
  {
    "front": "be given",
    "back": "kureru",
    "createdAt": 1740159152257
  },
  {
    "front": "start",
    "back": "hajimeru",
    "createdAt": 1740159166255
  },
  {
    "front": "get up",
    "back": "okiru",
    "createdAt": 1740159175269
  },
  {
    "front": "spring",
    "back": "haru",
    "createdAt": 1740159183882
  },
  {
    "front": "morning",
    "back": "gozen",
    "createdAt": 1740159191614
  },
  {
    "front": "different",
    "back": "betsu",
    "createdAt": 1740159202311
  },
  {
    "front": "where",
    "back": "doko",
    "createdAt": 1740159208838
  },
  {
    "front": "room",
    "back": "heya",
    "createdAt": 1740159215197
  },
  {
    "front": "young",
    "back": "wakai",
    "createdAt": 1740159224245
  },
  {
    "front": "car",
    "back": "kuruma",
    "createdAt": 1740159230938
  },
  {
    "front": "put",
    "back": "oku",
    "createdAt": 1740159236963
  },
  {
    "front": "reside",
    "back": "sumu",
    "createdAt": 1740159245367
  },
  {
    "front": "work",
    "back": "hataraku",
    "createdAt": 1740159258570
  },
  {
    "front": "difficult",
    "back": "muzusashii",
    "createdAt": 1740159276961
  },
  {
    "front": "teacher",
    "back": "sensei",
    "createdAt": 1740159283058
  },
  {
    "front": "stand",
    "back": "tatsu",
    "createdAt": 1740159296109
  },
  {
    "front": "call",
    "back": "yobu",
    "createdAt": 1740159305388
  },
  {
    "front": "university",
    "back": "daigaku",
    "createdAt": 1740159322397
  },
  {
    "front": "cheap",
    "back": "yasui",
    "createdAt": 1740159331858
  },
  {
    "front": "more",
    "back": "motto",
    "createdAt": 1740159345938
  },
  {
    "front": "go back home",
    "back": "kaeru",
    "createdAt": 1740159356171
  },
  {
    "front": "understand",
    "back": "wakaru",
    "createdAt": 1740159366983
  },
  {
    "front": "wide",
    "back": "hiroi",
    "createdAt": 1740159376463
  },
  {
    "front": "number",
    "back": "suu",
    "createdAt": 1740159382855
  },
  {
    "front": "near",
    "back": "chikai",
    "createdAt": 1740159397778
  },
  {
    "front": "there",
    "back": "soko",
    "createdAt": 1740159404133
  },
  {
    "front": "run",
    "back": "hashiru",
    "createdAt": 1740159410513
  },
  {
    "front": "put in",
    "back": "ireru",
    "createdAt": 1740159418374
  },
  {
    "front": "teach",
    "back": "oshieru",
    "createdAt": 1740159430014
  },
  {
    "front": "walk",
    "back": "aruku",
    "createdAt": 1740159436359
  },
  {
    "front": "meet",
    "back": "au",
    "createdAt": 1740159443372
  },
  {
    "front": "write",
    "back": "kaku",
    "createdAt": 1740159450049
  },
  {
    "front": "head",
    "back": "atama",
    "createdAt": 1740159458727
  },
  {
    "front": "sell",
    "back": "uru",
    "createdAt": 1740159469079
  },
  {
    "front": "enjoy",
    "back": "daiski",
    "createdAt": 1740159497555
  },
  {
    "front": "body",
    "back": "karada",
    "createdAt": 1740159506273
  },
  {
    "front": "at once",
    "back": "sugu",
    "createdAt": 1740159512087
  },
  {
    "front": "fly",
    "back": "tobu",
    "createdAt": 1740159518763
  },
  {
    "front": "very",
    "back": "totemo",
    "createdAt": 1740159524941
  },
  {
    "front": "who",
    "back": "dare",
    "createdAt": 1740159529870
  },
  {
    "front": "favorite",
    "back": "suki",
    "createdAt": 1740159536454
  },
  {
    "front": "read",
    "back": "yomu",
    "createdAt": 1740159544459
  },
  {
    "front": "next",
    "back": "tsugi",
    "createdAt": 1740159552287
  },
  {
    "front": "you",
    "back": "anata",
    "createdAt": 1740159560200
  },
  {
    "front": "drink",
    "back": "nomu",
    "createdAt": 1740159566948
  },
  {
    "front": "old",
    "back": "furui",
    "createdAt": 1740159574237
  },
  {
    "front": "question",
    "back": "shitsumon",
    "createdAt": 1740159582714
  },
  {
    "front": "today",
    "back": "kyou",
    "createdAt": 1740159596349
  },
  {
    "front": "friend",
    "back": "tomodachi",
    "createdAt": 1740159602600
  },
  {
    "front": "early",
    "back": "hayai",
    "createdAt": 1740159612513
  },
  {
    "front": "which",
    "back": "dore",
    "createdAt": 1740159636020
  },
  {
    "front": "beautiful",
    "back": "utsukushii",
    "createdAt": 1740159650199
  },
  {
    "front": "always",
    "back": "itsumo",
    "createdAt": 1740159658797
  },
  {
    "front": "leg",
    "back": "ashi",
    "createdAt": 1740159666838
  },
  {
    "front": "wake up",
    "back": "okosu",
    "createdAt": 1740159677525
  },
  {
    "front": "show",
    "back": "miseru",
    "createdAt": 1740159684951
  },
  {
    "front": "daughter",
    "back": "musume",
    "createdAt": 1740159691957
  },
  {
    "front": "enjoy",
    "back": "tanoshimu",
    "createdAt": 1740159700169
  },
  {
    "front": "color",
    "back": "iro",
    "createdAt": 1740159707529
  },
  {
    "front": "everybody",
    "back": "minna",
    "createdAt": 1740159716027
  },
  {
    "front": "take",
    "back": "toru",
    "createdAt": 1740159721595
  },
  {
    "front": "study",
    "back": "benkyou",
    "createdAt": 1740159730325
  },
  {
    "front": "can do",
    "back": "dekiru",
    "createdAt": 1740159744102
  },
  {
    "front": "short",
    "back": "mijikai",
    "createdAt": 1740159764689
  }
]